netwrix.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. We have established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit our Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. We strive to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, we intend to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

## Our Uses of Personal Information

We collect Personal Information including contact information (such as name, email address, and phone number) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date and security code), when you purchase or download our software products through our Website using a credit or debit card. Please note that Netwrix does not directly collect or store your financial account information – instead, we use a reputable company (the "Payment Processing Company") to collect and process your payment information. Rest assured, however, that we have taken steps to ensure that the Payment Processing Company protects Personal Information it collects from you in compliance with our Privacy Policy. We use the Personal Information we collect from you in connection with processing your order and providing you with support (if you have purchased support) and other information related to the product you have purchased/downloaded. We may also collect Personal Information when you contact us with questions, comments or requests for information and we will use the information you provide in such communications to respond to you. We may use the Personal Information you provide at the time of product purchase/download to periodically send news, bulletins or other marketing information to you. If we choose to send such marketing communications, you will have the ability to opt out of receiving some of them. 

We also collect Personal Information through our software. The phone home feature of our software collects usage information related to the software for purposes of license validation, auditing, and verifying compliance with licensing terms – to the extent Personal Information is included in phone home data, we will only use it internally in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may also collect Personal Information through our software in connection with our Customer Experience Program. Through the Customer Experience Program, we will collect user activity data and logs detailing your activity in connection with the software and other statistical information about your use of the software and its functions, and we will aggregate such usage data for the purposes of generating statistical metrics and analytics regarding use of the software – We use commercially reasonable efforts to anonymize data collection through the Customer Experience Program, however, to the extent any Personal Information is inadvertently included in Customer Experience Program usage data, we will only use it internally in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not want us to collect Customer Experience Program usage data, you can expressly opt-out of the Netwrix Customer Experience Program during installation of the software or by changing your preferences in the “Software Options” after installation of the software.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

## Security

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within our company or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

## Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to us and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

## Opting Out

Because we respect privacy rights, we allow you to opt out of receiving certain information. If we choose to send news, bulletins or other marketing information or communications to you, we will provide you with the ability to decline, or opt out of, receiving such communications, and we will take reasonable steps to comply with such requests in a timely manner. Instructions for opting out will be provided if and when we determine to send such a communication. Please understand that you will not be allowed to opt out of formal notices concerning the operation of our Website, and legal and other related notices concerning your relationship to us and the products you have purchased/downloaded.

## Third Party Services

Third parties provide certain services available on this web site. We may provide information, including Personal Information that we collect on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which we maintain our Web site and mailing lists. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on our behalf. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on our behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against our policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

## Partners and Affiliates

We may transfer some parts of the collected information to our partners and affiliates. Partners play an important role in our operations: they help us market, sell and support our products and services. We take applicable steps to ensure that our partners and affiliates are required to protect your Personal Information on our behalf.

## Children's Privacy

We are not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Your Consent

By using this Web site or otherwise providing Personal Information in connection with the purchase/download of a Netwrix product, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to our processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where we collect Personal Information on the Web.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of the Netwrix Corporation who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us.

## Your European Union Privacy Rights

We adhere to local data protection laws in the European Economic Area, and in particular the General Data Protection Regulation. To learn more, click here.

## Links to Other Web Sites

This web site may contain links to other web sites and you should review the privacy policies on those sites. We have no responsibility for the policies and practices of those sites.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If significant changes are made in the way your Personal Information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

## Questions or Feedback

Contact us for any questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy.
